50  这个数字是在被Google Play命名的Android Market
50. That's how many apps were available in
第一次随着第一款Android设备在2008年推出时
Android Market as Google Play was named when
的商店中可用的应用程序的数量
it first launched alongside the first Android device
在几天之后  Android Market
in 2008. A few days later, Android Market
向所有的开发者开放注册并且
opened for all app developers to register and
在没有任何来自Google OEMs
start publishing their apps without any review or
或运营商的审查  验证  要求就开始发布它们的应用程序
validation requirements from Google, OEMs, or carriers. For
我们作为一个开发者  发布应用的可能性
us as developers, the ability to distribute apps and
和从中获利的可能在应用程序购买
the possibility of monetizing them through up front payments
和广告的收入到应用程序的开发者囊中在持续上升
in app billing and advertising directly to the owners of
并且在Android生态系统中拥有
over a billion android devices is one of the
超过十亿的Android设备是有非常多的机会获取收入的
most exciting opportunities made possible by the android ecosystem. Growing
我是成长在没有互联网和智能手机的年代
up the dark days before smartphones and the internet,
如果我想使用一个新的应用程序或者一款新哟许
if I wanted a new game or app I had
我不得不去实体店并且购买
to go to a physical store and pay for a
盒装的软盘或者光盘  作为开发者
cardboard box filled with floppy disks or CDROMs. As developers
很大一部分我们的商业计划当时是
a big part of our business plan back then
如何得到我们的软件的包装盒并把软件放到架子上
was how to get those boxes of our software onto
或者在移动设备的世界中  如何
those shelves. Or in the world of mobile, how
让运营商或OEM和我们达成协议
to secure a carrier or OEM deal to get our
把我们的应用程序预装到设备上
apps preloaded onto the devices. Today I can install
今天我可以安装一百多万个由成百上千的开发者
over a million apps of games created by tens if
通过Google Play提供的应用程序或游戏
not hundreds and thousands of developers via Google Play, all
只需要点击一个按钮即可完成  那将是上百亿的应用程序安装量
with a click of a button. That's translated into tens
发布推送应用程序给Android用户可以在数百个国家进行
of billions of app installs. An incredible opportunity to
这是一件令人难以置信的事情
distribute apps to Android users in hundreds of countries.
在Android的早期版本  快速的
Now, in the early days of Android, being fast
成功运行第一个程序是一个相当坚实的成功的策略
and launching first was a pretty solid strategy for success,
但是随着开始的50个应用程序迅速的增长到
but as those first 50 apps quickly grew to
上百  上千  甚至是现在超过一百万的应用程序
hundreds, thousands, and now over a million apps, it takes
需要在应用中脱颖而出成为佼佼者需要的不仅仅是速度
a lot more than speed to stand out in
最近的应用的品质事关重大
the crowd. These days the tables stakes are a base
并有一个愿意为所有用户提供良好的用户体验的基线
line of quality and willingness to create great experiences
当然应用的质量是具有主观性的
for all your users. Of course app quality can
但是多年来我们已经确定了
be somewhat subjective, but over the years we've identified
用户辨别一个应用是否为高质量应用的核心标准
the core criteria that users identify with apps of
为了让你浏览起来更加轻松
high quality. And to make your life easier, they're
它们已经在Android Developer站点上已经可以供你观看
all available on the Android developer site for you
Google Play的应用跟踪团队
to review. This is the same checklist that the
是确保应用的质量和特色
merchandising team for Google Play used to ensure only apps
在促销和编辑的选择分类中是相同的检查清单
of quality are featured in their promotions and
并且它们包括一切  从应用程序设计指南
editor's choice categories. And they include everything, from following
到支持不同的屏幕方向
the app design guidelines to supporting different screen orientations,
平板  和其他设备  当然是要确保
tablets, and other devices. And of course ensuring that
你的应用程序时稳定的和高性能的
your app is stable and performant. So, with over
所以  在Google Play有超过一百万的应用程序
a million apps already available in Google Play it's
已经不再只是一个数字游戏了  我们不需要
no longer just a numbers game. We don't need
更多的应用和游戏  甚至更多的开发者
just more apps or games, or even more developers.
我们所需要的是像你一样的高质量的伟大的应用开发者
What we want is high quality apps from great developers, like you.